[{"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b991", "question": "Mean Joe Greene helped what team win four Super Bowls?", "answer": "Pittsburgh Steelers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1fc", "question": "Who had an 1980's hit with the song \"Is There Something I Should Know\"?", "answer": "Duran Duran", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "596dfa21cf3977a46e7ce443", "question": "The abnormal fear of spiders is called what?", "answer": "Arachnophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600cc1ac6de0eb824d4052e1", "question": "The U.S. Virgin Islands are located in which Ocean?", "answer": "Atlantic Ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a39e", "question": "Which is bigger, the state of Florida or England?", "answer": "Florida", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bac4", "question": "What \"C\" word is the name for a two-hulled boat?", "answer": "Catamaran", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59da1b8ff6756c9b30ba14fa", "question": "What is the capital of Ukraine?", "answer": "Kiev", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa3f62c73aa70ea0b70aff", "question": "Pennsylvania has what patriotic motto?", "answer": "\"Virtue, Liberty and Independence\"", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca5f", "question": "What is a kookaburra?", "answer": "Bird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2dd", "question": "What year was actor Stan Laurel born?", "answer": "1890", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba1d", "question": "What was unusual about Dizzy Gillespie's trumpet?", "answer": "The bell was bent upwards", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff511daff04d658268c92cb", "question": "What Greek general is responsible for the project that generated most of the surviving structures on the Acropolis?", "answer": "Pericles\u00a0promoted the arts and literature, which made Athens the educational and cultural center of the ancient Greek world.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c09a", "question": "Epistemophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Knowledge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecd662ec223966ae8f88d2", "question": "On the TV show \"How I Met Your Mother\", what is Lily\u2019s occupation?", "answer": "Kindergarten Teacher", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be1d", "question": "What is the setting for the video game Fallout 3?", "answer": "Capital Wasteland/Washington D.C.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba8a", "question": "What\u2019s the Hungarian word for red pepper?", "answer": "Paprika", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5f3", "question": "Into which bay does the Ganges flow?", "answer": "The Bay of Bengal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac1b", "question": "When did the Seychelles gain their independence from the United Kingdom?", "answer": "June 29, 1975", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b7abbd76490a8cc1a6e5298", "question": "What is the maximum number of points one can achieve in the video game \"Pac-Man\"?", "answer": "3,333,360 points", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5cefc0ae948005ec986edcde", "question": "Who is the fifth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Vivi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f94", "question": "Which science fiction writer developed a series of ethics for robots known as the \"Laws of Robotics\"?", "answer": "Isaac Asimov", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7ca97877e98cb97778a07", "question": "Which city is Seattle's sister city in Japan?", "answer": "Kobe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b88d", "question": "In which city would you find Wembley stadium?", "answer": "London", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa6e", "question": "Port Said lies on which waterway?", "answer": "The Suez Canal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133958c", "question": "What song did Wayne and Garth listen to on their way to the doughnut shop in the movie \"Wayne's World\"?", "answer": "Bohemian Rhapsody", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f79", "question": "What was Marky Mark's backing band?", "answer": "The Funky Bunch", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59cdb22065ff7d326b622a71", "question": "What is the name given to the dish of dates, or prunes, wrapped in bacon?", "answer": "Devils on Horseback", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2e3", "question": "What peace activist was the emcee at Woodstock?", "answer": "Wavy Gravy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c437", "question": "What is the top layer of Earth called?", "answer": "Crust", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fffa78373838c5c8a417f39", "question": "What kind of animal is a bustard?", "answer": "Bird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ff1", "question": "Fred Astaire's character in \"Funny Face\" was based on what fashion photographer?", "answer": "Richard Avedon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339245", "question": "What is the birth country of Russell Crowe?", "answer": "New Zealand", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c322", "question": "How many continents are located entirely in the Southern Hemisphere?", "answer": "2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff2", "question": "What is the principle ingredient of the dish Biryani?", "answer": "Rice", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6010c6a50775fa611bce67d2", "question": "Which 1990s computer program was launched without company approval?", "answer": "AOL Instant Messaging -- \u00a0In May 1997, a group of engineers quietly released Instant Messaging without permission -- for free!", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a82a", "question": "What is the largest country in Africa in terms of land size?", "answer": "Algeria", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3bd", "question": "Why is \u00c5land known as the Islands of Peace?", "answer": "No military has entered it since Finnish takeover", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "597cdaaae347d002c297e4d6", "question": "What nationality is Yehudi Menuhin?", "answer": "American", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3c0dff048f679a45ab3b", "question": "Where can you find the \"pudu\", the world\u2019s smallest deer?", "answer": "South America", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e1", "question": "What is the name of the first book in the \"Bourne Trilogy\"?", "answer": "The Bourne Identity", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fef5e106ce05a3942286e2f", "question": "Which movie\u2019s sequel has the tagline \"Same make. Same model. New mission\"?", "answer": "\"Terminator\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5be", "question": "What gland secretes human growth hormone?", "answer": "Pituitary Gland", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392d6", "question": "In which TV show did a Mr. Hogg own a place called the \"Boar's Nest\"?", "answer": "The Dukes of Hazzard", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcc4", "question": "What is a fairy ring made of?", "answer": "Mushrooms", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2fe", "question": "What Danish peninsula lent its name to the largest naval battle of World War I?", "answer": "Jutland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5909cab7bb53d1af658864d1", "question": "On what short story was the 1946 film \"It\u2019s a Wonderful Life\" based on?", "answer": "The Greatest Gift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc1081469bb8041d07a06f", "question": "Which popular 1960's American car was affectionately known as \"The Goat\"?", "answer": "Pontiac GTO", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a55d", "question": "What US city is home to the Bishop Museum?", "answer": "Honolulu", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015e8f7fe83fe1f2a824be2", "question": "Which monarch appointed Pitt the Younger to the office of prime minister in December 1783?", "answer": "George III", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58b8cec194b094db915830aa", "question": "For which pen company did Josef Lamy work for before founding the Lamy pen company in 1930?", "answer": "Parker", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fffa86973838c5c8a417f3d", "question": "What common kitchen ingredient is crucial to the human body\u2019s chemistry?", "answer": "Salt (The human body contains many types of salts, but the primary is NaCL, or sodium chloride, also known as common table salt.)", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb83", "question": "What citrus beverage has used the ad slogan \"Open a Bottle of Sunshine\"?", "answer": "Sunny Delight", "category": "general"}, {"id": "595643fe803c1f1ebcc4a032", "question": "Ketchup was sold in the 1830\u2019s as what?", "answer": "Medicine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390f9", "question": "Who wrote the novels \"The Deceiver\" and \"The Fist of God\"?", "answer": "Frederick Forsyth", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bca9", "question": "What drink is made from fermented honey, yeast and water?", "answer": "Mead", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389e0", "question": "Who took Oliver Twist into his home even though he had been accused of picking his pockets?", "answer": "Mr. Brownlow", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd86", "question": "What type of animal is the Japanese monster, King Ghidorah?", "answer": "Three-headed dragon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a197", "question": "In the video game \"Darksiders\", which of the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse do you play?", "answer": "War", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a561", "question": "What Ivy League University is located in New Haven, Connecticut?", "answer": "Yale University", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe1f020145fb2946670738f", "question": "Popcorn comes in which two general shapes?", "answer": "Mushroom and butterfly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015e18cfe83fe1f2a824b96", "question": "Where was the French surrender to Germany signed?", "answer": "In a railway car", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c6f1877e98cb977789c5", "question": "Which East Asian country celebrates Golden Week?", "answer": "Japan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b513", "question": "What is mixed with Kahlua or Tia Maria to make a Black Russian?", "answer": "Vodka", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600b88ca1d8c1817608d53f7", "question": "What are the highest and lowest cards in Poker?", "answer": "Ace is highest and 2 is lowest.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdab4fa0b8cce1e6fda7049", "question": "What English word has the most definitions/meanings?", "answer": "Run", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338971", "question": "What sport was most frequently featured in Degas' paintings?", "answer": "Horseracing", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7ee", "question": "In the UK, what is called a \"courgette\"?", "answer": "A zucchini", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba96", "question": "The pasta shape called \"farfalle\" gets its name from the Italian word for what insect?", "answer": "Butterfly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58b36ee91c3f17ccc40c8e0b", "question": "What is Dr. Malcolm Crowe\u2019s profession in the film \"The Sixth Sense\"?", "answer": "Child psychologist", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5902a06bcad1ec93f27df76b", "question": "Which Bohemian city gave us the Pilsner?", "answer": "Pilsen", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4da", "question": "What is the largest country entirely within the Southern Hemisphere?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad9", "question": "What was the common archaic name for a giraffe?", "answer": "Camelopard", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389fb", "question": "Whose paintings include \"Two Half-Naked Women Seen from Behind in the Rue des Moulins Brothel\"?", "answer": "Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afa4", "question": "What year was Prince Charles invested as Prince of Wales at Caernarvon Castle?", "answer": "1969", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b69920de762b54eb9be941f", "question": "Who released the album \"The 20/20 Experience\" in 2013?", "answer": "Justin Timberlake", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdffcfd1cf6db9ac4808d07", "question": "What is the most populous city in Australia?", "answer": "Sydney", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5feb34897e83c707845b20cb", "question": "The \"Eddie Murphy Rule\" banned certain kinds of insider trading in commodities markets. It was inspired by Murphy\u2019s role in what film?", "answer": "Trading Places", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad0", "question": "What does a nephologist study?", "answer": "Clouds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe73503eec85e375820b241", "question": "On two separate occasions, President Ford was shot at by which two people?", "answer": "Lynette \"Squeaky\" Fromme and Sara Jane Moore", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8b39501dd7bf43be5e7b2", "question": "A group of herring is called what?", "answer": "An army", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a9e93917ccba3ffe45786c7", "question": "What is the \"Davy Lamp\" commonly referred to as?", "answer": "Miner's lamp", "category": "science"}, {"id": "594a63ea2ebb971c1417fb9e", "question": "Which famous classical composer's music was featured in the film \"Clockwork Orange\"?", "answer": "Beethoven's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6589bae7e414034b5aef3", "question": "Where did yoga originate?", "answer": "India", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cdc02e347d002c297e4e4", "question": "What is the capital of Belgium?", "answer": "Brussels", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff145dbb0ee8c595b6d39bc", "question": "The pen name of which American writer means \"two fathoms deep\"?", "answer": "Mark Twain", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6bc", "question": "What separates the twin cities of Minneapolis and Saint Paul?", "answer": "Mississippi River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe65c5c1f3c0ead6880d613", "question": "What are mummies wrapped in?", "answer": "Linen cloth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ccd", "question": "What line is missing from some bowdlerized edits of Van Morrison's \"Brown Eyed Girl\"?", "answer": "Making love in the green field", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e7a", "question": "Which TV show used the song \"A Little Less Conversation\" by Elvis Presley as its theme song?", "answer": "Las Vegas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c56f", "question": "Which Australian animal has unique fingerprints?", "answer": "Koala", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c410", "question": "DuPont chemist Wallace Carothers developed what new plastic material in 1930?", "answer": "Nylon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea7746ff048f679a45abc7", "question": "What does the scientist called a \"cytologist\" do?", "answer": "Study cells", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f45", "question": "What sheriff's alter ego was the masked \"El Kabong\"?", "answer": "Quick Draw McGraw's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4df", "question": "What fruit comes in Damson and Mirabelle variety?", "answer": "Plums", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7cd0c877e98cb97778a31", "question": "Where is the Whistler Ski Resort located?", "answer": "British Columbia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fbaead10738315b1fb74e2b", "question": "Diamondback and Timber are types of what animal?", "answer": "Rattlesnakes", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f80", "question": "What was Robyn Hitchcock's backing band?", "answer": "The Egyptians", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b566", "question": "What color moves first in checkers?", "answer": "Black", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d48", "question": "Theo, LeSieg and Rosetta Stone are some of the pen names used by what popular author?", "answer": "Dr. Seuss", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c88e64c22f44c2d77a29c40", "question": "What war hero, later the 7th American President, led the Americans to victory in the Battle of New Orleans?", "answer": "Andrew Jackson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fefa55a6ce05a3942286ebf", "question": "What was Arnold Schwarzenegger's character's name in the film \"Total Recall\"?", "answer": "Dennis Quaid", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a095", "question": "What was the name of Punky Brewster's dog?", "answer": "Brandon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c687", "question": "What is the average lifespan of the hummingbird?", "answer": "5 years", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8eb", "question": "How many colored squares are there on a standard Rubik\u2019s cube?", "answer": "54", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394c0", "question": "What \"Pink Panther\" director produced the TV show \"Peter Gunn\"?", "answer": "Blake Edwards", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015e5b3fe83fe1f2a824bc3", "question": "In what country was the first electro mobile produced?", "answer": "Austria", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b6b", "question": "What future Oscar-winning actress played the title role on the 1960's sitcom \"Gidget\"?", "answer": "Sally Field", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a725", "question": "Mount Whitney is the highest peak in which mountain range?", "answer": "Sierra Nevada Range", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a3c83c4039f3d7859290ffb", "question": "In the TV Show \"Gunsmoke\", who portrayed deputy Chester Goode?", "answer": "Dennis Weaver", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a162c03f01ec323f849172d", "question": "What is the largest island in the Caribbean?", "answer": "Cuba", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb77", "question": "What is the name for the type of scissors which produce a zig-zag cut when cutting fabric?", "answer": "Pinking shears", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af83", "question": "Which US president asked the US congress to declare war on Japan in 1941?", "answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6014c8defbde8045e48466e2", "question": "What do plants produce through photosynthesis?", "answer": "Plants use energy from the sun to turn carbon dioxide into food. Carbohydrates and oxygen are the end result of photosynthesis.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b75", "question": "In \"Napoleon Dynamite\", what type of animal is Napoleon's grandmother's pet, Tina?", "answer": "llama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b571c9167df192a942e3376", "question": "What is Pele's birth name?", "answer": "Edson Arantes do Nascimento", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398bc", "question": "What rapper was born Marshall Bruce Mathers III?", "answer": "Eminem", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8a97d01dd7bf43be5e74e", "question": "In chess, the queen has the combined movement of which two pieces?", "answer": "Bishop and Rook", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe0e562fcbed638185eaa2e", "question": "Where can you take part in the \"Battle of the Oranges\"?", "answer": "Ivrea, Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e147f3f6ca6dac04a20ca53", "question": "The Harry Nilsson song \"Gotta Get Up\" was frequently used in which Netflix original series?", "answer": "Russian Doll", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fb0", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"The Turn of the Screw\"?", "answer": "Henry James", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c3e9a9febfabb9c85d8a97d", "question": "What is the fear of odors known as?", "answer": "Olfactophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab1778baab681b09292182", "question": "What numbers appear on Donald Duck\u2019s car plate?", "answer": "313", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339046", "question": "What year did Wagner compose \"Tannhauser\"?", "answer": "1845", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339031", "question": "Jim Rhodes is the alter ego of which Marvel comic book hero?", "answer": "War Machine", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bee", "question": "Where does the Bossa Nova dance music originate?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133946b", "question": "What movie earned Katharine Hepburn her last Oscar?", "answer": "On Golden Pond", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b70a", "question": "According to Irish superstition, what stands open during the 12 days of Christmas?", "answer": "The gates of heaven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1c2", "question": "Which politician is known as Tarzan?", "answer": "Michael Heseltine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58b371481c3f17ccc40c8e1e", "question": "Approximately how much more beer would you get in a pint served in the UK compared to one served in the US?", "answer": "95 mL", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3e2", "question": "Which city in Tennessee is the country music capital?", "answer": "Nashville", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6a0df20565ad31a57c79c", "question": "Which US President had the first phone installed at the White House?", "answer": "Rutherford Hayes", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b297", "question": "Under what Roman pseudonym were the Federalist Papers written?", "answer": "Publius", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feb33a97e83c707845b20c4", "question": "Guy Bailey, Roy Hackett and Paul Stephenson made history in 1963, as part of a protest against a bus company that refused to employ black and Asian drivers in which UK city?", "answer": "Bristol", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390f2", "question": "Who is typically referred to as \"The Father of History\"?", "answer": "Herodotus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dca", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by The New Christy Minstrels?", "answer": "Green, Green", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdabd210b8cce1e6fda7061", "question": "What is the body of the DMC DeLorean car made out of?", "answer": "Stainless steel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58b8cf2994b094db915830ad", "question": "The Bical grape originates from which European country?", "answer": "Portugal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e05", "question": "What show debuted on September 7, 1979, with George Grande anchoring?", "answer": "SportsCenter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffb5c795dad637d903c881e", "question": "\"Ital\" is the word used to describe the cuisine of which group of people?", "answer": "Rastafarians", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef5bde6ce05a3942286e19", "question": "The Jeffersons\" was a spinoff of what show?", "answer": "\"All in the Family\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a15e", "question": "What is the occupation of Mary Poppins?", "answer": "Nanny", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad7d", "question": "Which enemy of the Roman Empire was nicknamed the \"Scourge of God\" by the Catholic Church?", "answer": "Attila the Hun", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133963f", "question": "In which country was Greta Garbo born?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7e1", "question": "What do SETI programs search for?", "answer": "Extraterrestrial Intelligence", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fb0875acf631c2414a13b56", "question": "In \"Game of Thrones\", what are the three names of Daenerys\u2019 dragons?", "answer": "Drogon, Viserion, and Rhaegal", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133987e", "question": "In Star Wars, what kind of a farm does Luke Skywalker grow up on?", "answer": "Moisture farm", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa52b2c73aa70ea0b70b1d", "question": "What Caribbean island is known as \"Little England\"?", "answer": "Barbados", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ff6", "question": "What is Johnny Chase's nickname on the TV show \"Entourage\"?", "answer": "Drama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0b3", "question": "The term Sesquincentennial represents how many years ?", "answer": "150", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f73", "question": "What vehicle was driven by Caractacus Potts?", "answer": "Chitty Chitty Bang Bang", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fbc", "question": "The critical clue in what movie turns out to be a Japanese gardener complaining that salt water is \"bad for glass\"?", "answer": "Chinatown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab1b2aa4fda37788a9a1dbc", "question": "Scotophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Darkness", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133970b", "question": "What is Woody Allen's birth-name?", "answer": "Allan Stewart Konigsberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4e7b506d333868d34d741", "question": "In 1929, what did Clarence Birdseye introduce?", "answer": "Frozen food", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59564396803c1f1ebcc4a030", "question": "Which two sisters are the only ones to win the ACM\u2019s Top Female Vocalist award?", "answer": "Loretta Lynn and Crystal Gayle", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bece", "question": "In the game of cricket which bird name means scoring no runs?", "answer": "Duck", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef59a56ce05a3942286e05", "question": "Walnut Grove, Minnesota is the setting for which television series?", "answer": "\"Little House on the Prairie\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b398", "question": "Who founded the American Red Cross?", "answer": "Clara Barton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b57f", "question": "What is a group of crows called?", "answer": "A murder", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f56", "question": "What did the Elf Hermy want to be in the movie \"Rudolph, the Red-Nosed Reindeer\"?", "answer": "Dentist", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7759ceec85e375820b30e", "question": "Where are Zinfandel grapes from?", "answer": "Croatia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7f5", "question": "What's the common name for batteries that contain zinc and manganese dioxide?", "answer": "Alkaline batteries", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c1d", "question": "What were the last two letters added to the english alphabet?", "answer": "J and U", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7cf8e877e98cb97778a50", "question": "Until 1820, Maine was part of which US state?", "answer": "Massachusetts", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600242ee4be4723ccac2218f", "question": "In Jane Austen\u2019s \"Pride and Prejudice\", what is the name of the pompous clergyman who marries Elizabeth\u2019s sister, Charlotte?", "answer": "Mr. Collins", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8d5", "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Yukon river?", "answer": "US", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60121bae63c99d48cd169b0f", "question": "An ailurophile is a lover of what?", "answer": "Cats -- \"Ailurophile\" comes from the Greek \"ailouros\", for cat, combined with \"-phile\", the suffix for love.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be83", "question": "What instrument did bandleader Glenn Miller play?", "answer": "Trombone", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96fae23c87fd04dd15e44", "question": "Which Christmas song was actually written for Thanksgiving?", "answer": "\"Jingle Bells\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2cf", "question": "Who played the role of Julia Brougham in the 1947 film \"The Bishop's Wife\"?", "answer": "Loretta Young", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59071cdd3745b36be73039d1", "question": "Who worked as the lead Soviet rocket engineer during the Space Race between the United States and the Soviet Union?", "answer": "Sergei Korolev", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c817", "question": "What would a doctor call \"pes planus\"?", "answer": "Fallen arches", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58f1694af7c52aae91cc07cf", "question": "Which 1868 novel is often considered the first full length, English language detective novel?", "answer": "The Moonstone", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c53", "question": "\"Martin Chuzzlewit\" and \"The Olde Curiosity Shoppe\" are novels by what author?", "answer": "Charles Dickens", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba06", "question": "What sport did George Bush Sr. play at Yale University?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a1b", "question": "Will Smith, Charlize Theron, and Jack Lemmon were all featured in what movie?", "answer": "The Legend of Bagger Vance", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe1f341145fb29466707399", "question": "What candy bar originally came in three pieces and had three different flavors?", "answer": "3 Musketeers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a64c", "question": "Which US state is home to Arches National Park?", "answer": "Utah", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59bb2911c9bff04efae6d754", "question": "In what 1967 film did Gene Hackman earn his first Oscar nomination?", "answer": "Bonnie and Clyde", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6017375e44491cbd7c5a1789", "question": "Who designed and built the interior structure of the Statue of Liberty?", "answer": "The innovative designer and builder Gustave Eiffel and his structural engineer, Maurice Koechlin designed and built the statue.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394ae", "question": "Who created the TV series \"Twin Peaks\"?", "answer": "David Lynch and Mark Frost", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae1f", "question": "The Russian Mensheviks were opposed to what other faction?", "answer": "Bolsheviks", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133923a", "question": "What superhero sidekick is known as Boy Wonder?", "answer": "Robin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c812", "question": "What is the nearest spiral galaxy to our own Milky Way?", "answer": "The Andromeda Galaxy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6008dcd9f4f3bc4a292f861c", "question": "What college did Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. attend at the age of 15?", "answer": "Morehead College (He skipped the 9th and 12th grades, and enrolled in the same college his father and grandfather attended.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f1c", "question": "Who has been played in a movie by both Norma Shearer and Kirsten Dunst?", "answer": "Marie Antoinette", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b685e662d71a53651009", "question": "What French ballet term means \"in front\"?", "answer": "Devant", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6008e05cf4f3bc4a292f8631", "question": "What artist said, \"Every child is an artist\"?", "answer": "Pablo Picasso (The full quote reads,\u00a0\"Every child is an artist, the problem is staying an artist when you grow up.\")", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58c9f706b4e2c7fbd3896745", "question": "What is Kahlua flavored with?", "answer": "Coffee", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3cefff048f679a45ab44", "question": "Which animal can cause a tularemia infection in humans while being skinned for cooking purposes?", "answer": "Rabbits", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ddf", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"alcohol\"?", "answer": "Arabic", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3662ff048f679a45ab0c", "question": "\"Squab\" is a name given to the young of which bird?", "answer": "Pigeon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "597cddb5e347d002c297e4f3", "question": "Which 1960s singer/songwriter was voted \"Ugliest Man on Campus\" while attending college?", "answer": "Janis Joplin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c883", "question": "What popular computer language shares its name with the vitamin formerly known as ascorbic acid?", "answer": "C", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae10", "question": "Which city hosted the 2004 Summer Olympic Games?", "answer": "Athens", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cac4", "question": "What is the name for the number 1 followed by 100 zeros?", "answer": "Googol", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a924", "question": "In what country is Magyar spoken?", "answer": "Hungary", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60121d2863c99d48cd169b1b", "question": "The \"Maman\" sculpture in Bilbao, Spain is a giant what?", "answer": "Spider - The huge arachnid is modeled after the artist Louise Bourgeois\u2019s mother. It was her representation of her weaver mother.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b04", "question": "Which goddess started the Trojan War?", "answer": "Eris", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133900c", "question": "Which Italian dramatist wrote the play \"Accidental Death of an Anarchist\"?", "answer": "Dario Fo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b38e", "question": "Which crew sank in the 1978 Boat Race?\u00a0", "answer": "Cambridge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aebb", "question": "Who was the first man to swim the English channel?", "answer": "Matthew Webb", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b559", "question": "What are Persian apples known as today?", "answer": "Peaches", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9ec", "question": "The Kung San people live in what area of Africa?", "answer": "Kalahari Desert in Botswana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59008f86cf842fa4c4ba96bc", "question": "Who is the Roman Patron Saint of hangovers?", "answer": "Saint Bibiana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdf5", "question": "What Clorox \"formula\" was named in honor of its inventor's birthday, April 9?", "answer": "409", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5e0", "question": "What type of creature is a copperhead?", "answer": "A snake", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d2c", "question": "The title for the novel \"A Brave New World\" was derived from which Shakespearean play?", "answer": "The Tempest", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339203", "question": "Who finds E.T.?", "answer": "Elliott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcae", "question": "What kind of fruit juice is used to mix a Mojito?", "answer": "Lime", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5963726b967692ea851899bf", "question": "Approximately 95% of the jellyfish's body is made up of what?", "answer": "Water", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fecc0bfec223966ae8f885f", "question": "Charlie Brown's father was a what?", "answer": "Barber", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4ba", "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Costa Rica and Honduras?", "answer": "Nicaragua", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3d5", "question": "A male swan is called a what?", "answer": "Cob", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f1", "question": "What Agatha Christie novel was made up of two parts - England and Egypt?", "answer": "Death on the Nile", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c9fa877e98cb977789ff", "question": "In what world capital will you find Ho Hoan Kiem, the Lake of the Restored Sword?", "answer": "Hamli", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399f3", "question": "What famous TV cops drove a 1974 Ford Torino?", "answer": "Starsky & Hutch", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339672", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is Seymour Skinner's real name?", "answer": "Armin Tamzarian", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea4032ff048f679a45ab66", "question": "To which part of physics does the Archimedes' Principle refer?", "answer": "Buoyancy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c846", "question": "In what organ of the human body would you find the fovea?", "answer": "The eye", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58dba204874c93a3298b212e", "question": "Innsbruck is the capital of which Austrian state?", "answer": "Tyrol", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133913e", "question": "Whose final opera was called \"Death in Venice\"?", "answer": "Benjamin Britten", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5d8", "question": "How many fluid ounces in a gill?", "answer": "5", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5af259acb63e5727cf5a4851", "question": "Which rock band released the singles \"Karma Police\" and \"Creep\"?", "answer": "Radiohead", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59049a05cf93664eb1048696", "question": "The Queensland nut is another name for what nut?", "answer": "Macadamia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf2d", "question": "What is the eighth month of the year?", "answer": "August", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe69d4320565ad31a57c776", "question": "In medieval Scotland, what was a \"Gaberlunzie\"?", "answer": "A formerly-licensed beggar", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a7b", "question": "In Nathaniel Hawthorne's \"The Scarlet Letter\", what was the letter and what did it stand for?", "answer": "A for adultry", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338901", "question": "What is the name of the paranoid android in the book \"The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy\"?", "answer": "Marvin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c717", "question": "What inert gas gets trapped in the blood when a diver gets \"the bends\"?", "answer": "Nitrogen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b492", "question": "Which country were the 1896 Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "history"}, {"id": "594a633f2ebb971c1417fb98", "question": "Which Queen of England, and wife of Henry VIII, had six fingers on one of her hands?", "answer": "Anne Boleyn", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca76", "question": "How many yards are there in an imperial fathom?", "answer": "2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a273", "question": "Who was the male star of the 1997 film \"Titanic\"?", "answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a694", "question": "Which country contains the most forested area?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a255", "question": "What country was Alfred Hitchcock born?", "answer": "England", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4c8", "question": "What is a male donkey called?", "answer": "A jack", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a22c", "question": "Who played the title role in the 1981 film \"Mad Max 2\"?", "answer": "Mel Gibson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd66284a5bfecdd737e0845", "question": "What was Mickey Mouse originally called?", "answer": "Mortimer Mouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c3ce877e98cb97778997", "question": "Where are the Admiralty Islands?", "answer": "Papua New Guinea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339218", "question": "What is the theme song of the TV show \"Friends\" called?", "answer": "I'll Be There for You by The Rembrandts", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4bf", "question": "In medicine, what does the abbreviation LASIK stand for?", "answer": "Laser-Assisted In Situ Keratomileusis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6008db6ef4f3bc4a292f8617", "question": "Which country first settled land that would become the colony of Delaware?", "answer": "In 1638, Swedish settlers founded the first colony of New Sweden, which was later taken over by the Dutch and then the British.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a8e", "question": "Who created the character Conan the Barbarian?", "answer": "Robert E. Howard", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7be", "question": "What are the four southernmost states that border Nebraska?", "answer": "Missouri, Iowa, Kansas and Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59412836bab1e6f9796f1b5b", "question": "In the world of music, how is Leslie Sebastian Charles more commonly known as?", "answer": "Billy Ocean", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58d116744fea7fe947a22270", "question": "Who played the role of Veronica Quaife in the 1986 film \"The Fly\"?", "answer": "Geena Davis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ecc", "question": "What baseball player is Santiago's hero in \"The Old Man and the Sea\"?", "answer": "Joe DiMaggio", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397be", "question": "What 1980's band had fans that happily called themselves \"blockheads\"?", "answer": "New Kids on the Block", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133922a", "question": "What Welsh songstress has performed the themes for three different Bond movies?", "answer": "Shirley Bassey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ce4", "question": "Which \"Friends\" character is the answer to the trivia question in the SNL \"Lazy Sunday\" sketch?", "answer": "Matthew Perry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339645", "question": "Where did Kevin's parents go for Christmas in the 1990 movie \"Home Alone\"?", "answer": "France", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecd86fec223966ae8f88dc", "question": "What actor\u2019s face inspired \"Halloween\" baddie Michael Myers\u2019 mask?", "answer": "William Shatner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d86", "question": "What famous rapper's real name is Marshall Mathers?", "answer": "Eminem", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c7e", "question": "What fictional pirate commanded the Jolly Roger?", "answer": "Captain Hook", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396a2", "question": "Who played the role of Harold Payne in the 1994 movie \"Speed\"?", "answer": "Dennis Hopper", "category": "entertainment"}]